



### **EDUCATION**

**Bachelor of science** 

Osun state university

2016-2020

# **LANGUAGES**

English

Hausa

### **PROFILE**

I am a qualified and professional web developer with two years of experience in database administration and website design. Strong creative and analytical skills. Team player with attention to detail.



Front-end Development



Website Design



Web Coding



Wireframe Creation

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Senior Web Developer at Wardiere Inc.

October 2020-Current

- Editing, authoring, or developing Website content, as well as directing content-creation team members.
- Backup files from websites to local folders for disaster recovery.

# Web Developer at Studio Shodwe

February 2015-September 2019

- Creating, constructing, or maintaining websites and software applications.
- · Using scripting or writing languages, management tools, content creation tools.